#### Contact

+2348030405214 (Mobile) ekaokone@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ekaokone (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Data Visualization
Office Administration
Python (Programming Language)

### Languages

Efik (Full Professional)
Ibibio (Native or Bilingual)
English (Native or Bilingual)
Annang (Full Professional)
French (Limited Working)

### Certifications

Python Programming Language
Web Design and Development
Introduction to Machine Learning
Python Programming/Data Analysis
Data Entry Course

# **Ekaette Emmanuel Okon**

Physicist || Data Analyst || Machine Learning || Data Science || Administrative Officer || Open to Work || Open to Remote Roles Port Harcourt

# Summary

Experienced Professional Freelancer with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Analytical Skills, Administration, Data Visualization, Office Administration, and Database Management System (DBMS). Strong media and communication professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Physics from University of Port Harcourt.

# Experience

Self-employed
Professional Freelancer
March 2020 - Present (2 years 3 months)
Online

- \* Perform a variety of accounting
- \* Collecting and processing records, reports, and documents and entering them into a database or another information collection system.
- \* General Transcription
- \* Typing and converting of MS Word to Pdf and vice versa etc
- \* Web Research
- \* Data Mining
- \* Microsoft Office suite
- \* General Administration
- \* Google Docs
- \* Data Entry
- \* Data Collecting
- \* JPEG/PNG to Excel or Word conversion
- \* Data Scrapping
- \* Lead Generation
- \* CRM Data Entry
- \* Word Press Data Entry
- \* Data Collection from social media
- \* Data Cleansing
- \* E-commerce Products Listing on any Platform

- \* Property Research
- \* Public Record Research
- \* Copy Pasting
- \* Business Card and Shopify Data Entry

### Canet International School

**Teacher** 

September 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 4 months)

Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

\*Planned, prepared and presented engaging lessons for the pupils.

\*Organized and beautify the classrooms with learning resources that improved comprehension and assimilations.

\*Deployed content-focused method of education that boosted pupils learning.

\*Integrated technology based instruction and feedback system that heightened pupil's performance.

Embassy of the Republic of Guinea Administrative Assistant January 2013 - June 2014 (1 year 6 months) Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

\*Provided administrative support to ensure effective and efficient daily operations.

\*Managed document retrieval and archiving, received and organized incoming mails; maintained confidential records, and embassy databases.

\*Attended external meetings, adhere to general office protocol and procedures.

\*Liaised with diplomats, local staff and administrative attaché to provide effective communication.

Embassy of the Republic of Guinea Secretary to the Ambassador March 2010 - November 2012 (2 years 9 months) Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria \*Filed classified and unclassified materials, received and followed up on phone calls; attended to visitors, provided timely and responsive administrative support.

\*Managed documentation and informed the Ambassador of matters requiring attention.

\*Planned and scheduled travel itineraries for the Ambassador and for the staff of the Embassy.

\*Scheduled appointments/meetings for the Ambassador internally and externally.

\*Maintenance of Ambassador's diary, sent and received correspondences.

## Education

University of Port Harcourt

Bachelor of Science - BS, Physics · (January 2016 - July 2021)

Annang Secondary Commercial School WASSC, Science · (January 2000 - June 2006)